

# COSTA ANTON

**GRADUTE STUDENT** 

#### **HELLO**

I'm Costa, a developer from Bucharest

I am an open-minded individual who consistently strives to attain new knowledge and new experiences. Curiosity has always pushed me forward to try new things and I, without fail, have the perseverance to finish what I start. Apart from the education at universities in Romania I have done one semester in Krakow in Poland and 1 year of study in the Netherlands, both part of an ERASMUS scholarship.

# **EXPERIENCE**

July 2017 - August 2017

## **FIDA Solutions**

Summer intern

Summer internship, worked 6 weeks with JavaScript, HTML and CSS.  $\label{eq:css}$ 

March 2018 - September 2018

### **Property Shark**

Full Time Intern

A six-month period of internship. One half of it working with Visual Basic to do User Acceptance Tests. The second half was with C# creating and modifying ASP.NET applications. Both of them related the "PropertyShark - Real Estate Search and Property Information " website.

January 2019 - June 2019

# **Pragmatic Play**

Full time Programmer/Localisation Engineer
Unity developer for slots games. My task was to create Unity
editor extensions, or to continue existing extensions, to help
streamline the game production. I was also part of the
localisations team and we were responsible for the
maintenance of the application in the case that problems might
appear in certain languages.

July 2019 - September 2019

## University of Iceland

Placement Mobility European Economic Area(EEA)
A two-month mobility in Iceland to work at the university on a research project. I developed a Virtual Reality application in Unity to help people that suffer from Acrophobia (fear of heights).

## **EDUCATION**

| National College "Gheorghe Sincai"<br>Baia Mare, Romania  | 2011-2015 |
|---|-----------|
| Computer Science at University "Babes-Bolyai"   | 2015-2018 |
| Graphics, Multimedia and Virtual Reality<br>Master's Degree at "Universitatea<br>Politehnica din Bucuresti" | 2018-2020 |

#### VOLUNTEERING

#### **HERMES Society**

-Image and Public Relations Department Student organisation with members from the faculty of Mathematics and Computer Science of Babes-Bolyai.

### CONTACT

t: +40749759634

e: costa.anton@hotmail.com

#### SOCIAL

in www.linkedin.com/in/costa-anton-9b144410a

## **EXPERTISE**

| Java<br>Angular 2 | Intermediate<br>Intermediate |
|-------------------|------------------------------|
| C#                | Advanced                     |
| Python            | Intermediate                 |
| C++               | Intermediate                 |
| JavaScript        | Intermediate                 |
| Spring            | Beginner                     |
| Unity             | Advanced                     |
| Blender           | Beginner                     |
| Mava              | <br>Beginner                 |